(Sheldon:)Every year we'd
have a party.
(Sheldon:)No one I invited
would ever come,
(Sheldon:)because they didn't like me.
(Amy:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that part wasn't so bad.
(Sheldon:)I didn't like them, either.
(Sheldon:)But then I'd inevitably spend
(Sheldon:)the whole day being tortured
by my sister's friends.
Oh, you poor thing.
(Sheldon:)When I was six, they told me
Batman was coming to my party.
(Sheldon:)I waited by the
door for hours.
(Sheldon:)Closest thing
to Batman I saw
(Sheldon:)was when a robin
flew into the window.
(Amy:)You realize none of those things
would happen now?
(Sheldon:)I do, but why do you care
(Sheldon:)if I celebrate
my birthday at all?
(Amy:)Well, you made
my last birthday so memorable,
I wanted to return the favor.
PENNY:
Yeah, if you had
(Penny:)a party now, you
have plenty of friends
(Penny:)that would love to come.
(Leonard:)And we live here,
so we have no choice.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)You may celebrate my life
by throwing a party
(Sheldon:)with cake, presents and a
shower of admiration and love.
(Sheldon:)But then you owe me big-time.